# SIJITA SAKARIA 07907624214 Sijita73@gmail.com

#### RESUME

### **CERTIFIED MEDICAL CODER**

**CPC-A(88%)** 

4 years of nursing experience

### **SUMMARY**

 Hardworking and motivated medical coder seeking a full-time position. Good knowledge in ICD-10 CM, CPT coding, medical terminology and anatomy. Worked in hospitals and have over 4 Years of nursing experience. Familiar with patient health records and hospital care settings.

## **EDUCATION**

- Bachelor in Nursing
- Medical Coding Course (Magnet Medical Coding Solutions)

### <u>SKILLS</u>

- Knowledge in ICD-10 CM and CPT coding guidelines
- Familiar with medical terminology across a broad range of medical practice areas
- Basic understanding of physiology
- The ability to communicate on a professional level
- Fluent in English, Hindi and Malyalam
- Microsoft Office (basic skills)
- High ethical standards

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### eMDs (Noida)

Jan 2022-Present

• Experience in denial coding, SNF E&M. EMR worked on Aprima.

#### **HOM INDIA PVT LTD (Noida)**

Sep 2021-Dec 2021

• Worked as an Outpatient E &M coder .EMR worked on Caretracker

#### MAX HEALTHCARE, DELHI

Sep 2009-Oct 2012

- Directly involved with patient care
- Assisting physicians
- Health education

#### P.G. COLLEGE OF NURSING, MADHYA PRADESH

Oct 2007-Jan 2009

- Worked as a Clinical instructor demonstrating procedures
- Taught Subjects like Anatomy, English.

### PERSONAL DETAILS

NAME-Sijita Sakaria

**SEX-Female** 

LANGUAGES KNOWN-English, Hindi and Malyalam

**MARITAL STATUS-Married** 

**COMPUTER KNOWLEDGE-MS OFFICE(Basic Skills)** 

**LOCATION-Delhi**